foreign
action on the D Street starting with the
Benchmark index moves moving on to the
sectoral indices and also the individual
stocks that are moving the most in trade
as well let's look at how the markets
are trading before we go ahead and get
you the expert views as well the census
is down by 137 odd points at this point
in time hovering near 59 588 talk about
the Nifty as well that's down by 40 odd
points at 17 620 odd levels that's a cut
off almost two tenths of percent at this
point in time let's look at the broader
markets that have been holding the forts
through the trading session but are they
also looking at the selling pressure
really going on yes they are they've not
slipped towards the closing uh towards
the lower pointer of the day as well
about point zero seven percent of a
decline for the small cap 100 index
let's also look at how the mid cap
Hunter index is pairing slightly better
off but absolutely flat in trade with a
negative bias there has been just a
recovery in the last few or trading
seconds as well as far as the mid cap
100 index is concerned but it's the
Nifty it index that's been the biggest
culprit in today's trading action
dragging the overall sentiments on the D
Street with respect to the Benchmark
indices as well the Nifty it continues
to drag uh right ahead of crucial
numbers of Q4 coming out some with some
you know Bellwether companies like HCL
technologies that will be reporting its
numbers tomorrow but this reaction is as
a follow-up to infances TCS and the
earnings downgrades that we are seeing
HCL Technologies meanwhile down by 2.2
percent towards the day's low right
ahead of the numbers so some more
nervousness as far as the it pack is
concerned we'll take the experts view on
the it path as well but for now what's
doing well in this otherwise lackluster
Market is Metals which are shining
brighter about half what percent up in
trade point six percent of an upside can
actually be seen on that one apart from
this you do have some other sectors as
well that are absolutely flat in trade
very very choppy the auto sector is flat
absolutely the Pharma index has been
holding on to some positive gains and
still is up about 0.21 in trade right
now but not too much of gains also
coming in right here mixed trade as far
as the Nifty bank is concerned with
respect to financial services PSU Banks
and the private Banks the oil and gas is
in fact moved to the higher point of the
day 0.2 percent uptick for the Nifty oil
and gas base so keep an eye out on that
as well slight gains coming in on the
royalty pack as well but we'll see how
the markets really shut up about 20
minutes remaining for the markets to
shut up in today's trading action as
well let's welcome our guest on the show
deepam Sharma joinson he's the
co-founder of green portfolio Mr Sharma
good afternoon and thank you so much for
taking the time out for this discussion
first up by your take on the market
Outlook we've been seeing two or three
trading sessions of consolidation will
this continue for some more time before
we actually see a movement on the top
and what will it really take for the
markets to come out of this
consolidation Zone
so actually uh we are looking at uh so
post RBI action uh earlier this month uh
we had seen a rally in the markets and
we are now seeing some bit of
consolidation in the markets as uh we
have already seen a good rally uh we
believe that next trigger for the
markets would be the U.S fed action and
uh that uh if if the FED holds the it
this time it will be a very positive uh
move for the markets and uh but for
India perspective we believe that the
the tables have turned and the sentiment
has turned positive uh from that aspect
uh we have already seen some bit of
positiveness coming from the FBI action
and remember when the FBI's come into
the markets they will take the markets
to rise yeah so so we believe that it's
it's a good positive Market but waiting
for a U.S fed to follow up on stopping
the great hikes yeah what about the it
pack and how are you assessing the
earnings that have come through already
uh the earnings downgrades that have
come for some of the stocks like Infosys
for example we did see a sharp reaction
on an intraday level as far as post
results interaction was a reaction was
concerned but the markets have still not
been able to come out of that zone uh
despite the kind of move that we've been
able to see on some of the other indices
as well because most of the other big it
majors are still remaining to come out
with their earnings in fact all the it
stocks are down in the red right now as
we speak your own thoughts on the it
pack how are you looking at them
see we believe that this is the last leg
of panic uh in the ID sector we have
already seeing uh we have already seen
I.T stocks bleeding over the last one
year uh like we believe that this uh
like like what we feel is that the uh
order book Outlook uh the Panic for that
has already been priced in and say
another five seven percent or ten
percent kind of a correction will be a
good value by opportunity for the ID
stocks although having said that we
believe that uh it could take another
three to six months uh for the I.T
stocks to to settle down and then start
a rally again but ID sector looks really
promising if you look at it from the
next two to three years standpoint
okay and amid the earnings season where
exactly are you really taking positions
as of now some of the sectors where you
are bullish and on the other hand where
are you looking at some underperformance
creeping in how would you really advise
investors to really move ahead and
strategize their moves ahead of the Q4
numbers
see despite the markets uh despite the
Nifty index stocks uh slightly under
consolidation phase what we are seeing
is uh in the past few days a lot of
small cap and mid cap stocks have done
exceedingly well there are a lot of
stocks which have gone in Upper circuits
and uh the reason behind it is valuation
comfort so if you look at the valuations
of small and mid cap the price to
earnings have in a lot of spaces reached
the 2020 lows so we believe that a lot
of value opportunities have come up in
the small and mid cap you have to be
selective but there are a lot of
multi-pagger opportunities that have
come up you have to look at sectors like
Parma chemicals which have not seen or
run over the last uh two weeks two to
three years and have corrected the
fundamentals have still been intact but
the valuations have corrected more than
the fundamental drawdown so we believe
that sectors like Pharma chemicals
textile infra infra we believe that
there's a lot of focus on infra and
related sectors and that should do well
we believe that auto component should do
well uh so so you have to look at
sectors where there is import
restriction and there is export so China
plus one beneficiaries a lot of very
small companies are benefiting big time
uh increasing their capacities
multi-fold uh when they are benefiting
from import restrictions from China and
Export opportunities to the rest of the
world so so there are a lot of uh value
opportunities
you have to be stock specific
I think you should look at the broader
markets while investing in these times
okay I also wanted to ask you about some
of the stocks that have been in momentum
so far this week you know we did see ITC
crossing the 400 Mark for the first time
reaching an all-time high then we saw
dlf reaching its 52-week high as well
amidst the movement that we are seeing
in the royalty pack as well divis
Laboratories from the Pharma pack has
been leading for last few trading
sessions as well how are you looking at
some one or two three names that I've
just taken from there each respective
sectors as we speak
see uh fmcg we believe that uh the rural
stress
has almost been priced in and gradually
uh that rural consumption should come in
uh over the coming months we still
believe that most of the value
opportunity out of ITC has already been
played out uh you you still have to
remember that it's a conglomerate play
where there are a large like there are
two three key businesses uh which which
the company has so you'll not get
exactly valuations of an FM series talk
over there uh which are high multiples
so we believe that uh till the time we
get a good uh like uh and and also not
to forget that we do not have
a management uh that is uh that is then
that there there's no like there is
professional management but there is no
uh as such any family running the show
So that obviously tends to uh get the
company into a discount
so ITC uh we believe that most of the
value play has played out and uh there
is not much run left in the stock from
the Pharma standpoint device lab we
believe that it's a great story and uh
it should do well the farmer story has
just started and it should do really
well going forward
hmm okay understood that what about
these new age Tech socks uh some of them
are again coming on the top brokerage
houses radar like a zomato for example
that was up in trade uh some of the
broken houses have come out with reports
looking at a 30 upside from the current
levels as well uh now we get to see how
the Q4 really pans out for these new age
talks but some of them had started to
show some kind of positive sentiment in
the last quarterly earnings as well are
you looking at positively in any of the
stocks from this realm
see there could be some trading bounces
in these stocks uh over the next few
months as the markets rally uh but from
a long-term standpoint we believe that
profitability is the key the kind of
investors that you get when you are
unlisted and the kind of investors that
you get when you're listed they are
completely different mindsets so if you
are looking at investing in these new
age stocks definitely they have created
a mark definitely they have grown they
have uh like they have a great market
share and these players are here to stay
but if you are eyeing for a re-rating in
the stocks you
the profitability to come on a
Consolidated level and that to sustain
so uh investors should rather wait for
the profitability to actually come and
they might be uh like paying 10 20 30
extra at those times but then you have
more certainty so for the new age stocks
I would say it's still a weight and
watch let's see how zomato delivers a
profitability by 2025 and when it
actually comes then invest
okay understood that well thank you so
much Mr Sharma for being with us and
discussing with us all these various
talks and sectors where opportunities
can be scouted by investors in this
current very very choppy and
consolidating kind of a market scenario
that we are looking at right now let's
look back at how the markets are trading
at this point in time still about 130
points of a loss for the sensex is
trading below 59 600 miles about a cut
of 133 odd points the Nifty is down by
40 odd points and it's now hovering near
17 600 kind of a level a quarter percent
of a fall for this one but we are still
about 12 minutes away from the market
close of the day we'll keep our watch on
how the markets are moving at this point
in time and how do they shop could be
perhaps the third consecutive session
where we do see a muted closing for the
markets but we'll keep an eye and so
should you be with us on business today
TV continue to engage with us on our
social media platforms as well to catch
all the updates from the world of stock
markets until then thanks for tuning in
foreign
[Music]
ladies and gentlemen on Tech today we
have a very special guest in fact one of
our most special guests yet on the show
I'm joined by none other than Tim Cook
Tim what a pleasure to me what a
pleasure to be here and hello everyone
hello but we got a namaste moment when
you did open the first Apple Store over
here